♪Come closer♪
اقترب ♪
♪Be more intimate♪
♪ كن أكثر حميمية
♪Tell me if I am tempted♪
♪ قل لي إن كنت أغوى
♪The moment you and I looked at each other♪
♪ في اللحظة التي نظرت فيها أنا وأنت إلى بعضنا البعض
♪We were both tempted♪
كلانا أغوى
♪Remember how shy you were♪
♪ تذكر كم كنت خجولًا ♪
♪That day♪
♪ ذلك اليوم ♪
♪Sweet memories♪
♪ ذكريات حلوة ♪
♪Please be more♪
♪ من فضلك كن اكثر
♪How lucky I am to have you♪
♪ كم أنا محظوظ لوجودك ♪
♪So sweet♪
♪ حلوة جدا ♪
=My Naughty Assistant=
= مساعدي المشاغب =
=Episode 17=
= الحلقة 17 =
Be gentle.
كن لطيفآ.
You hurt me.
آذيتني.
I've told you that Liang Jiawei is not a good man.
لقد أخبرتك أن ليانغ جياوي ليس رجلاً صالحًا.
Do you know that you were in danger?
هل تعلم أنك في خطر؟
I was not.
لم اكن.
Not?
لا؟
You were almost...
كنت على وشك ...
I won't mind
لن أمانع
your business anymore.
عملك بعد الآن.
Whatever.
ايا كان.
(What a fickle man.)
(يا له من رجل متقلب).
Dinner time.
وقت العشاء.
I'm on a diet.
أنا في حمية.
I can't eat.
لا أستطيع أن آكل.
Here.
هنا.
Let me take a look.
دعني ألقي نظرة.
It's fine now.
كل شيء على ما يرام الآن.
Let's have dinner.
دعنا نتناول طعام العشاء.
Smells great.
رائحته رائعة.
But you've cooked too much.
لكنك تطبخ كثيرًا.
Bacon and fried egg.
بيكون و بيض مقلي.
Well,
نحن سوف،
it will taste better
سيكون طعمه أفضل
with wine.
مع النبيذ.
Feed me.
أطعمني.
Which piece?
أي قطعة؟
There's something in the corner of your mouth.
هناك شيء ما في زاوية فمك.
Where is it?
أين هي؟
Xing Enchen!
Xing Enchen!
I want to have steak too.
أريد شريحة لحم أيضًا.
Come on.
هيا.
Slow down.
ابطئ.
♪How many times in my life♪
♪ كم مرة في حياتي ♪
♪I am destined♪
أنا مقدر ♪
♪To meet you and fall in love with you♪
♪ لمقابلتك والوقوع في حبك
♪In my finest age♪
♪ في خيرة عمري ♪
♪It's a pity♪
♪ إنه لأمر مؤسف
♪That we are not together in this life♪
بأننا لسنا معًا في هذه الحياة
♪But still, thank you♪
♪ لكن مع ذلك ، شكرًا لك ♪
♪For letting me♪
♪ لسماحك لي ♪
♪Walk into your world♪
♪ امش في عالمك ♪